[Music]
i
thought my world was ending my bed was
empty and the sky was gray
ever since you went away
that's over I’ve done a lot of
thinking and maybe too much drinking
maybe not
still I know now what I’ve got
I’ve got a lot of other people who will
care enough to see me through another
day
[Applause]
I'm feeling lucky
[Music]
I'm looking
all the time it would make me lose my
mind
whatever I’ve grown a whole lot stronger
don't need you any longer don't know why
i couldn't tell the truth from a lie
but now I’ve come to the conclusion that
our love is
you should have been
[Music]
God I wanted you to stay
I'm feeling so much better now
so I wouldn't have it
other way
[Music]
so now I’ve come to the conclusion that
our love is an illusion
and it's over I'm feeling lucky
I'm feeling looking
[Music]
you should
I'm looking at a strong
[Music]
it would make me lose my mind
whatever I’ve grown a whole lot stronger
i couldn't tell the truth from a lie
but now I’ve come to the conclusion that
our love is
[Music]
I'm feeling lucky
i fell apart when you walked out
God I wanted you to stay
[Music]
I'm feeling so much better now
so I wouldn't have it any other
[Music]
anyway
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
you should have bet the long shot
you could have won the whole part
I'm feeling lucky
[Music]
you said i'd die without you
and that i'd cry about you all the time
it would make me lose my mind
whatever I’ve grown a whole lot stronger
don't need you any longer I don't know
why I couldn't tell the truth from a lie
[Music]
I'm lucky
I'm feeling lucky